# Stefan Brunotte

# Junior Full Stack Developer

I am a creative, professional, practical, and technically minded Junior Full Stack Developer. I am excited to move into a full-time technical position in Stockholm. I primarily code in Python but I also have some experience in JavaScript. I bring valuable additional experience from the world of financial trading in the futures markets as well as from the Crypto Currency markets.

# Most Significant Experience

19/02/10 - 20/06/31

## Full Stack Developer

First Class Honors Diploma, Code Institute, Dublin - Ireland

The Full Stack Web Developer course is a comprehensive introduction to software development with important coding languages that make up frontend and backend development.

Throughout the duration of my course I developed and deployed four projects, these projects included: *Frontend development*, *Backend* development and *Database* management. All projects used Git and GitHub for version control and the projects were deployed via Heroku.

World of Shape - <a href="https://worldofshape.herokuapp.com/">https://github.com/MrBrunotte/worldofshape</a>)

This project is built with the Django 3 framework with an MTV architecture pattern. From the Admin dashboard CRUD operations can be conducted in all 7 apps. Stripe payment method was used for a fully functional payment system. To ensure security of the site, I have used the built-in protection against CSRF attacks. Testing was conducted on each app with Django's TestCase and SimpleTestCase framework.

**Technologies used**: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Django3, JQuery, SQLite and Heroku Postgres.

Foodictionary - <a href="https://foodictionary.herokuapp.com/">https://foodictionary.herokuapp.com/</a>
(<a href="https://foodictionary.herokuapp.com/">https://foodictionary.herokuapp.com/</a>
(<a href="https://foodictionary.herokuapp.com/">https://foodictionary.herokuapp.com/</a>

This project focused on building a site for a user that needs to store data. MongoDB was used to create and store the values and the CRUD functions was used for all recipes. I used Pythons built in Unit Testing Framework for testing my project.

Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Flask, JQuery, MongoDB.

Vacation Explorer - <a href="https://mrbrunotte.github.io/Vacation-Explorer/">https://mrbrunotte.github.io/Vacation-Explorer/</a> (<a href="https://github.com/MrBrunotte/Vacation-Explorer">https://github.com/MrBrunotte/Vacation-Explorer</a>)

This project focused on building a site that depends on API's. I have used the Google Maps Platform where I worked with the Maps JavaScript API and the Places API. The site lets the user find hotels, bars and restaurant in a chosen county and city. All locations within a 5K area are displayed and the user can scroll the map to update the locations when exploring the city.

 $\textbf{Technologies used:} \ \textit{HTML5}, \ \textit{CSS}, \ \textit{JavaScript}, \ \textit{Google Maps}, \ \textit{JQuery}.$ 

# Personal Info

Address

Skillinggränd 5, 112 20 Stockholm. Sweden

Phone

+46 708-240 243

@ E-mail

mrbrunotte@gmail.com

GitHub

https://github.com/MrBrunotte

in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/stefan -brunotte-44b01521/

### Interests

Trading

Personal Growth

Coding

Skiing

Family

Travel

Golf

# **Skills**

Team-player	••••
Positive Attitude	••••
Quick Learner	••••
People Skills	••••
Persistence	••••
High-End User Focus	••••
Time/Task Management	••••

# **Academic Qualification**

#### 2019/02 - 2020/06

# Code Institute - Dublin, Ireland

Full Stack Developer - First Class Honors Diploma

 Fully trained in all remote practices with a Diploma in Full Stack Development.

### 2018/08 - 2018/09

# Programming 1 & basic C#

#### Komvux

• Introduction to programming with pseudocode, flowcharts and basic C#.

#### 2009/08 - 2011/06

## Master in Banking & Finance

Stockholm School of Economics - Stockholm, Sweden

 Portfolio theory, Corporate Finance theories, and Financial derivatives and their applications. Econometrics and financial modelling and their applications. Financial institutions in a global context, and using financial information in the decision making process.

### 2008/01 - 2009/06

# Bachelor of Science, Business Administration

Stockholm School of Economics - Stockholm, Sweden

Political economy, bachelor's thesis and other economy related courses.

#### 2003/08 - 2005/02

# **Estate Agency Program**

Gävle högskola - Gävle, Sweden

· Basic estate agency, sales and marketing.

# **Work History**

### 2005/01 - Current

# **Discretionary Futures Day Trader**

Part-time Day Trader - Stockholm, Sweden

 Part-time futures day trader that regularly and routinely trade the future and crypto markets using my own custom build discretionary PA analysis.
Currently building and converting my trading plan into a semi-automated trading software

### 2015/04 - 2018/11

# Care Assistant

Attendo IOF - Stockholm, Sweden

 Management, supervision, and support for young unaccompanied minors who are refugees here in Sweden.

#### 2014/05 - 2014/11

### **Real Estate Agent**

Siw Kraft Mäkleri AB - Stockholm, Sweden

• Real estate agent for high-end penthouses in Stockholm.

### 2005/03 - 2007/06

### Real Estate Agent and 7-eleven franchisee

Erik Olsson Fastighetsförmedling - Stockholm, Sweden

 Real estate agent, selling both houses and apartments in the Stockholm metropolitan area.

### 2000/01 - 2003/08

# 7-eleven franchisee

Seven Eleven franchisee - Stockholm, Sweden

# Software

Python	••••
JavaScript	••••
C#	••••
HTML5	••••
CSS	••••

# Frameworks / Libraries

Django	••••
Flask	••••
Bootstrap	••••
Materialize	••••
jQuery	••••

# Source Control / IDE

Git	••••
GitHub	••••
Visual Studio	••••
Visual Studio Code	••••

# **Database**

Mongo DB	••••
MySQL	••••
Heroku Postgres	••••

# **Design Tools**

Adobe Xd	••••